<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sahil Shah</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sahil Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&#39;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&#39;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&#39;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/blog/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/blog/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&#39;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>college_resume</title>
      <link>/college_resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/college_resume/</guid>
      <description>Sahil B. Shah (832) 782-7923 | sahil2699@gmail.com | 910 W 25th Apt 405, Austin, TX 78705 Education The University of Texas at Austin The University of Texas at San Antonio Major: Computational Biology Minors: Computer Science and Applied Statistical Modeling Overall GPA: 3.6623/4.00 UT GPA: 3.5143/4.00 August 2018 - Present August 2017 - May 2018 Pre-Professional Experience Dr. Claus O. Wilke Lab, Undergraduate Researcher June 2019 - Present • Computationally research viral genomic patterns to determine gene regulatory mechanisms TIDES Fellowship, Undergraduate Researcher June 2019 - July 2019 • Computationally research viral genomic patterns to determine gene regulatory mechanisms Virtual Cures ARI, Undergraduate Researcher January 2019 - Present • Research potential cures for Plasmodium vivax through virtual screening and wet lab techniques MOVE San Antonio, Intern January 2018 - June 2018 • Fundraise for the organization, organize community events, and register citizens to vote Texas Mission of Mercy, Volunteer October 2017 - Present • Assist dentists with dental procedures and bring in patients to the operating room Texas Periodontists, Intern Dental Assistant June 2018 - August 2018 • Assist dentists with dental procedures, X-rays, and sterilization UTSA Brush Rush, Volunteer October 2017 - May 2018 • Teach elementary school students about dental hygiene BAPS Shri Swaminarayan Temple Health Fair, Volunteer September 2017 • Assist dentists with dental screenings MD Anderson Cancer Center, Intern July 2016 • Assisted an anesthesiologist with caring for a patient’s needs • Observed medical procedures performed by various surgeons Extracurricular Activities UT Austin Sanger Learning Center, PLUS Facilitator January 2019 - May 2019 • Lead discussions and teach material in biochemistry to students Organic Chemistry Tutor, Tutor September 2018 - December 2018 • Tutor college students in Organic Chemistry Indo-American Forum of Fort Bend, Volunteer August 2013 - May 2019 • Help setup and plan multicultural events for the community Elections Office of San Antonio, Voter Registrar September 2017 - May 2018 • Registering voters in Bexar County UTSA GlobeMed, Member August 2017 - May 2018 • Fundraise for Sacred Valley Health to create a self-sustaining community in Peru St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>